<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GDSCACE</string>
    <string name="grow_title">Grow</string>
    <string name="grow_desc">Apply new learnings to build great solutions for local problems. Advance your skills, career, and network. Give back to your community by helping others learn, too.</string>
    <string name="learn_title">Learn</string>
    <string name="learn_desc">Learn about a range of technical topics and gain new skills through hands-on workshops, events, talks, and project-building activities - both online and in-person.</string>
    <string name="connect_desc">Meet students interested in developer technologies at your university. All are welcome, including those with diverse backgrounds and different majors.</string>
    <string name="connect_title">Connect</string>
    <string name="gdsc_desc">Google Developer Student Clubs is a Developers program for university students to learn mobile and web development skills, design thinking skills and leadership skills.</string>
    <string name="Opp">Opportunities GDSCs provide students with</string>
    <string name="member">Become a Member</string>
    <string name="codelab">Codelab</string>
    <string name="techtitle1">Android Development</string>
    <string name="techtitle2">Web Development</string>
    <string name="techtitle3">Cloud Computing</string>
    <string name="techtitle4">Machine Learning</string>
    <string name="techtitle5">Cyber Security</string>
    <string name="techtitle6">Robotics</string>
    <string name="techtitle7">Augmented Reality</string>
    <string name="eventtitle1">Jetpack Compose Camp</string>
    <string name="eventtitlefor1">Beginner</string>
    <string name="techdesc1">Every year Google developers release exciting new updates to the world\'s most popular operating system. We always have sessions to keep you updated and mastering the latest trends in modern Android development.</string>
    <string name="techdesc2">Learn the core foundations of a delightful web experience both for the user and developer. Stay up to tabs with emerging and trending technologies. Get access to a guided, tutorial and hands-on coding experience.</string>
    <string name="techdesc3">For passionate developers who want to stay relevant in a cloud first world where businesses demand for agility and innovation and prompt rise of cloud-native applications to bridges gaps between data, insight, and action.</string>
    <string name="techdesc4">Learn how to drive user engagement and retention with intelligent apps that are able to effectively serve users what they need without the fuss by providing these systems with the ability to automatically learn and improve from experience without being explicitly programmed.</string>
    <string name="techdesc5">With exponential rise in digital world, the attacks are rising more and more. Learn how to keep your applications safe in this world of information technology.</string>
    <string name="techdesc6">Robotics can take on a number of forms. A robot may resemble a human, or it may be in the form of a robotic application, such as robotic process automation (RPA), which simulates how humans engage with software to perform repetitive, rules-based tasks.</string>
    <string name="techdesc7">Augmented reality (AR) is the integration of digital information with the user\'s environment in real time.</string>
    <string name="leadname1">Amey Pandit</string>
    <string name="leadname2">Mahendra Yadav</string>
    <string name="leadname3">Aarnav Sangekar</string>
    <string name="leadname4">Hitanshu Oza</string>
    <string name="leadname5">Ria Kokate</string>
    <string name="leadname6">Ritik Yadav</string>
    <string name="leadname7">Anjan Yadav</string>
    <string name="leadname8">Bhagyadeep Pawaskar</string>
    <string name="leadname9">Dhairya Honrao</string>
    <string name="leadname10">Gautam Suvarna</string>
    <string name="leadname11">Manan Jotangia</string>
    <string name="leadname12">Sahil Nilkanth</string>
    <string name="leadname13">Gaurav Konde</string>
    <string name="leadname14">Hrigved Suryawanshi</string>
    <string name="leadname15">Atharva Shirke</string>
    <string name="leadname16">Shubham Dhopat</string>
    <string name="leadname17">Avishkar Dige</string>
    <string name="leadname18">Gautam Mishra</string>
    <string name="leadname19">Vedant Dandge</string>
    <string name="leadrole1">GDSC Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole2">Android Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole3">AR|VR|Game Development Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole4">AI|ML Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole5">AI|ML Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole6">Web Dev Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole7">Cloud Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole16">Cloud Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole8">Data Science Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole17">Data Science Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole9">Robotics Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole14">Robotics Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole15">Design Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole10">Cybersecurity Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole13">Cybersecurity Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole11">Marketing Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole18">Marketing Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole12">Web Dev Lead</string>
    <string name="leadrole19">Android Lead</string>
    <string name="ques1">Who can become a member?</string>
    <string name="ques2">How frequently do events and workshops occur?</string>
    <string name="ques3">What should I carry when attending a workshop?</string>
    <string name="ques4">Who should I reach out to if I have any questions?</string>
    <string name="ans1">The clubs is open to any student, ranging from novice developers who are just starting, to advanced developers who want to further their skills.</string>
    <string name="ans2">We have a hands-on session every Tuesday at SG25 from 1800hrs to 2030hrs. We also hold workshops and showcases. We would recommend you to join our community to get updates.</string>
    <string name="ans3">We recommend you carry with you a notebook, pen and a laptop because more often than not we make our hands dirty with code. Most importantly, carry along a healthy dose of curiosity and enthusiasm.</string>
    <string name="ans4">If you have any questions or comments, please don\'t hesitate to contact us by clicking the button below. We would be happy to stay engaged via email even after the event</string>
</resources>